<<<<<<< HEAD
const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'Which one of these is not a javascipt framework or library ?',
    options: ['React', 'Angular', 'Laravel', 'jQuery', 'Vue'],
    correct: 'Laravel',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Which one of these is odd one out ?',
    options: ['MySql', 'PostgreSQl', 'MariaDB', 'Cassandra', 'None of these'],
    correct: 'Cassandra',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'Which HTTP status code represents conflict response condition ?',
    options: ['401', '501', '200', '409', 'None of these'],
    correct: '409',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'Which type of JavaScript language is ___',
    options: [
      'Object-Oriented',
      'Object-Based',
      'Assembly-language',
      'High-leve',
    ],
    correct: 'Object-Based',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      ' In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:',
    options: [
      'Syntax error',
      'Missing of semicolons',
      'Division by zero',
      'Missing of Bracket',
    ],
    correct: 'Division by zero',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      'Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?',
    options: ['toString()', 'valueOf()', 'toLocaleString()', 'toPrecision()'],
    correct: 'valueOf()',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:',
    options: [
      'Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.',
      'Both are x and y are equal in value only.',
      'Both are equal in the value and data type.',
      'Both are not same at all.',
    ],
    correct: 'Both are equal in the value and data type.',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      'In JavaScript, what will be used for calling the function definition expression:',
    options: [
      'Function prototype',
      'Function literal',
      'Function calling',
      'Function declaration',
    ],
    correct: 'Function literal',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      'Which one of the following is used for the calling a function or a method in the JavaScript:',
    options: [
      'Property Access Expression',
      'Functional expression',
      'Invocation expression',
      'Primary expression',
    ],
    correct: 'Invocation expression',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'Which one of the following is an ternary operator:',
    options: ['?', ':', '-', '+',],
    correct: '?',
  },
=======
const questions =  [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which one of these is not a javascipt framework or library ?",
        options: ["React", "Angular", "Laravel", "jQuery", "Vue"],
        correct: "Laravel"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which one of these is odd one out ?",
        options: ["MySql", "PostgreSQl", "MariaDB", "Cassandra", "None of these"],
        correct: "Cassandra"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which HTTP status code represents conflict response condition ?",
        options: ["401", "501", "200", "409", "None of these"],
        correct: "409"
    }
>>>>>>> df75820b51b1950dad02f552e80570c343193be4
]

export default questions;